The first kill is the hardest.
The Chosen is a horror, thriller film directed by Ben Jehoshua.
When a child-stealing demon attaches itself to a little girl, her family is thrust into a
battle against time in order to save the girl and send the demon back to hell.
Cameron, played by Kian Lawley.
Eliza, played by Elizabeth Keener.
Caitlin, played by Angelica Rose Torres.
Uncle Joey, played by Chris Gann.
Aunt Jean, played by Dayna Devon.
Officer Jehoshua, played by Wiley B. Oscar.
The Chosen is a 2015 American horror film starring YouTube
personality Kian Lawley and Elizabeth Keener.
The screenplay was written by Barry Jay Stitch, Andrew
Scheppmann, and Ben Jehoshua, who also directed.
The film was produced by Joe Dain, Miles Fineburg, and Jim Klock.
It was released on July 24, 2015.
The Chosen is Lawley's first feature film starring role.
The tone is dark and intense.